jobsdb.com 2014-06-24

# None

jobsDB Hong Kong pledges to meet fully with the requirements of the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance, Chapter 486 of the Laws of Hong Kong. In doing so, jobsDB Hong Kong will ensure compliance by its officers and staff to the strictest standards of security and confidentiality in respect of all personal information and data submitted by users via the Site and jobsDB Hong Kong will not, subject to the terms herein, release such information to anyone without the prior consent of the relevant user(s) of the Site (whether registered or not) (" **Users(s)** ") except to the authorized persons listed under the section headed " **Disclosure or Transfer of Data** ".

Users are strongly recommended to read this Privacy Statement carefully to have an understanding of jobsDB Hong Kong's policy and practices with regard to the treatment of personal information and data provided by the Users on the Site. This Privacy Statement is applicable to both registered and unregistered Users, and the terms herein may be updated, revised, varied and/or amended from time to time as jobsDB Hong Kong may deem necessary and/or appropriate.

If Users have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, they should contact the Customer Support Executive of jobsDB Hong Kong's Customer Service Department, whose contact details are set out under the section headed " **Enquiries** " below.

In this Privacy Statement, the following terms shall have the respective meanings specified below unless the context otherwise requires:

" **Employer(s)** " means users seeking employees.

" **jobsDB** " means Jobs DB Inc.

" **jobsDB Hong Kong** " means Jobs DB Hong Kong Limited.

" **Job Seeker(s)** " means users seeking employment.

" **Site** " means any website or mobile application owned and operated by jobsDB and its affiliates/subsidiaries.

## Purpose of Collection of Personal Data

In the course of using the Site, Users may disclose or be asked to provide personal information and/or data. In order to have the benefit of and enjoy various services offered by the Site, it may be necessary for Users to provide jobsDB Hong Kong with their personal information and/or data. Although Users are not obliged to provide the information and/or data as requested on the Site, jobsDB Hong Kong will not be able to render certain services on the Site in the event that Users fail to do so. 

jobsDB Hong Kong's purposes for collection of the information and data on the Site include but not limited to the following: 

(a) for the daily operation of the services provided to Users;

(b) to assist Jobseekers to find appropriate employment with Employers and to assist Employers to assess the suitability of candidates for job vacancy for a wide spectrum of jobs and industries;

(c) to provide Users with various services offered by the Site and newsletters, job openings and promotional and marketing materials (for further details, please refer to section headed "Subscription of Newsletter/Promotional Materials/Marketing Materials" below); 

(d) to handle and follow up enquiries, requests and complaints from Users;

(e) to contact Users regarding administrative notices and communications relevant to his/her use of the Site and to respond to Users' inquiry or request;

(f) to assist jobsDB Hong Kong with developments for future marketing and promoting purposes or other internal purposes;

(g) to verify the identity of Users who have posted advertisements, materials, representations, messages, views or comments or such other information (collectively " **Information** ") on the Site; 

(h) to identify Users who have viewed the Information posted on the Site;

(i) to allow Users to enjoy their benefits as members of the Site by enrolling for special events and promotions hosted by jobsDB Hong Kong and or its affiliates and or partner company; 

(j) to identify Users who have enjoyed their benefits as members of the Site by receiving and using marketing promotional materials;

(k) to facilitate jobsDB Hong Kong and/or its affiliates to use the Users' personal data for the purposes relating to the provision of services offered by jobsDB Hong Kong and marketing services and/or special event of jobsDB Hong Kong and/or its affiliates;

(l) to obtain statistics about Users to analyze usage of the Site in order to help its further development for internal use; and

(m) for purposes other than the above mentioned which are related to jobsDB Hong Kong's and/or its affiliates' provision of their product and/or services as jobsDB Hong Kong may deem fit.

If a User is under the age of 13, jobsDB Hong Kong would strongly recommend him/her to seek prior consent from a person with parental responsibility for him/her, e.g. parent or guardian, who may contact the responsible Customer Support Executive whose contact details are set out under the section headed " **Enquiries** " for registering the User as member of the Site.

jobsDB Hong Kong strives to only collect personal data which are necessary and adequate but not excessive in relation to the purposes set out hereinabove.

If jobsDB Hong Kong requires the use of your personal data for a purpose other than those set out hereinabove, we may request your prescribed consent to the same. If you are a minor, the prescribed consent should be given by your parent or guardian.

## Collection of Personal Data

jobsDB Hong Kong may collect personal information and/or data about a User such as his/her name, log-in ID and password, address, email address, phone number, age, gender, date of birth, country of residence, nationality, education level and work experience that is/are not otherwise publicly available. Occasionally, jobsDB Hong Kong may also collect additional personal information and/or data from a User in connection with contests, surveys, or special offers.

Only duly authorized staff of jobsDB Hong Kong will be permitted to access Users' personal information and data, and jobsDB Hong Kong shall not release such personal information and data to any third parties save and except for the circumstances listed out under the section headed " **Disclosure or Transfer of Data** ".

## Disclosure or Transfer of Data

jobsDB Hong Kong agrees to take all practicable steps to keep all personal information and data of Users confidential and/or undisclosed, subject to the following.

Generally speaking, jobsDB Hong Kong will only disclose and/or transfer Users' personal information and/or data to jobsDB Hong Kong's personnel and staff for the purpose of providing services to Users and corporate clients of jobsDB Hong Kong who have made specific requests for such information and/or data with Users' prior consent. However, jobsDB Hong Kong may disclose and/or transfer such information and/or data to third parties under the following circumstances: 

(a) where the information and/or data is disclosed and/or transferred to any third party suppliers or external service providers who have been duly authorized by jobsDB Hong Kong to use such information and/or data and who will facilitate the services on the Site, under a duty of confidentiality;

(b) where the information and/or data is disclosed and/or transferred to any agents, affiliates or associates of jobsDB Hong Kong who have been duly authorized by jobsDB Hong Kong to use such information and/or data; 

(c) where permitted under the " **Terms and Conditions** "; 

(d) where jobsDB Hong Kong needs to protect and defend its rights and property;

(e) where jobsDB Hong Kong considers necessary to do so in order to comply with the applicable laws and regulations, including without limitation compliance with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Site;

(f) where jobsDB Hong Kong deems necessary in order to deliver the products and services that we offer and cultivate a positive user experience; and 

(g) where jobsDB Hong Kong deems necessary in order to maintain and improve the services on the Site.

Personal data collected via the Site may be transferred, stored and processed in any country in which jobsDB Hong Kong or its affiliates operate. By using the Site, Users are deemed to have agreed to, consented to and authorized jobsDB Hong Kong to disclose and/or transfer their personal information and data under the circumstances stated above, as well as to any transfer of information (including the Information) outside of the Users' country.

## Subscription of Newsletters/Promotional Materials/ Marketing Materials

jobsDB Hong Kong and its affiliates may from time to time send to members and Users of the Site newsletters, job openings and marketing materials based on the personal information and data that they have provided to jobsDB Hong Kong. jobsDB Hong Kong may use Users' data in direct marketing and jobsDB Hong Kong requires the Users' consent (which includes an indication of no objection) for that purpose. In this connection, please note that:

(a) the name, log-in ID and password, contact details, age, gender, date of birth, country of residence, nationality, education level and work experience of Users held by jobsDB Hong Kong from time to time may be used by jobsDB Hong Kong and/or its authorized personnel or staff in direct marketing;

(b) the following classes of services, products and subjects may be marketed:

i. travelling related products and services;

ii. job-hunting and agencies services offered other than by jobsDB Hong Kong;

iii. various courses and programs for Users seeking jobs and career opportunities;

iv. special events hosted by jobsDB Hong Kong and its affiliates for members and Users, including but not limited to courses, workshops, and competitions;

v. reward, loyalty or privilege programs and related products and services;

vi. special offers including coupons, discounts, group purchase offers and promotional campaigns;

vii. products and services offered by the Company's affiliates and advertisers (the names of such affiliates and advertisers can be found in the application form(s) for the relevant products and services, as the case may be);

viii. donations and contributions for charitable and/or non-profit making purposes;

(c) the above products, services and subjects may be provided or (in the case of donations and contributions) solicited by jobsDB Hong Kong and/or;

i. jobsDB Hong Kong's affiliates;

ii. third party service providers providing the products, services and subjects listed in paragraph (b) above; and

iii. charitable or non-profit making organizations;

(d) in addition to marketing the above services, products, and subject itself, jobsDB Hong Kong also intends to provide the data described in paragraph (a) above to all or any of the persons described in paragraph (c) above for use by them in marketing those services, products and subjects, and jobsDB Hong Kong requires the Users' written consent (which includes an indication of no objection) for that purpose; and

(e) jobsDB Hong Kong may receive money or other property in return for providing the data to the other persons in paragraph (d) above and, when requesting the Users' written consent as described in paragraph (d) above, jobsDB Hong Kong will inform Users if jobsDB Hong Kong receives any money or other property in return for providing the data to other persons.

Suitable measures are implemented to make available to such members the options to "opt-out" of receiving such materials. In this regard, Users may choose to sign up or unsubscribe for such materials by logging into the registration or user account maintenance webpage, or clicking on the automatic link appearing in each newsletter/message, or contact the Customer Support Executive of jobsDB Hong Kong, whose contact details are set out under the section headed " **Enquiries** ". 

## Access to or request for correction of data

Any User is entitled to request access to or make amendments to his/her own personal information and data kept with jobsDB Hong Kong by contacting the Customer Support Executive of jobsDB Hong Kong's Customer Service Department at whose contact details are set out under the section headed "Enquiries". Subject to the paragraph below, User may alternatively edit, amend or delete his/her personal information and data at any time by logging into the "MyJobsDB" section of the Site.

In the event that a User wishes to access or amend his/her personal information and data, jobsDB Hong Kong may request him/her to provide personal details in order to verify and confirm his/her identity. Identity card number or passport number or business registration certificate number cannot be amended unless such data is proved to be inaccurate. jobsDB Hong Kong is required to respond to User's requests within 40 days of his/her request and will endeavor to do so wherever possible, but jobsDB Hong Kong reserves the rights to charge the User a reasonable fee for doing so.

jobsDB Hong Kong will not retain your personal data if User requests jobsDB Hong Kong to cease his/her membership with jobsDB Hong Kong. We will only keep your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which the data was collected as set out under the section headed " **Purpose of Collection of Personal Data** ".

## Cookies and Log Files

jobsDB Hong Kong does not collect any personally identifiable information from any Users whilst they visit and browse the Site. When Users access the Site, jobsDB Hong Kong records their visits only and does not collect their personal information or data. The Site's server software will also record the domain name, server, address and track the pages Users visit and store such information in "cookies", and gather and store information like internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data in log files. All these are done without the Users being aware that they are occurring.

jobsDB Hong Kong does not link the information and data automatically collected in the above manner to any personally identifiable information. jobsDB Hong Kong generally uses such automatically collected information and data to estimate the audience size of the Site, gauge the popularity of various parts of the Site, track Users' movements and number of entries in jobsDB Hong Kong's promotional activities and special events, measure Users' traffic patterns and administer the Site. Such automatically collected information and data will not be disclosed save and except in accordance with the section headed " **Disclosure or Transfer of Data** ".

## Links to Other Sites

The Site may provide links to other websites which are not owned or controlled by jobsDB Hong Kong or its affiliates. Personal information and data from Users may be collected on these other websites when Users visit such websites and make use of the services provided therein. Where and when Users decide to click on any advertisement or hyperlink on the Site which grants Users access to another website, the protection of Users' personal information and data which are deemed to be private and confidential may be exposed in these other websites.

Non-registered Users who gain access to the Site via their accounts in online social networking tools (including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter and Sina Weibo) are deemed to have consented to the terms of this Privacy Statement, and such Users' personal data which they have provided to those networking tools may be obtained by jobsDB Hong Kong and be used by jobsDB Hong Kong and its authorized persons in and outside of the User's country for the purpose of providing services and marketing materials to the Users. jobsDB Hong Kong and its authorized personnel may gain access and use the personal data of such Users so obtained, subject to the other provisions of this Privacy Statement.

This Privacy Statement is only applicable to the Site. Users are reminded that this Privacy Statement grants no protection to Users' personal information and data that may be exposed on websites other than the Site, and jobsDB Hong Kong is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. Users are strongly recommended to refer to the privacy policy of such other websites.

## Testimonials

jobsDB Hong Kong posts Users' testimonials on the Site, which may contain personally identifiable information such as the Users' names. jobsDB Hong Kong does obtain the Users' consent prior to posting the testimonials to post their names along with their testimonials.

## Security

The security of Users' personal information and data is important to jobsDB Hong Kong. jobsDB Hong Kong will always strive to ensure that Users' personal information and data will be protected against unauthorized access. jobsDB Hong Kong has implemented appropriate electronic and managerial measures in order to safeguard, protect and secure Users' personal information and data.

All personal information and data provided by Users are only accessible by the authorized personnel of jobsDB Hong Kong or its authorized third parties, and such personnel shall be instructed to observe the terms of this Privacy Statement when accessing such personal information and data. Users may rest assured that their personal information and data will only be kept for as long as is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it is collected. Registered Users should safeguard his/her unique Username and Password by keeping it secret and confidential and never share these details with anyone.

jobsDB Hong Kong uses a third party service provider to facilitate the electronic payment transactions on the Site.

jobsDB Hong Kong follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and data submitted by Users to the Site, both during transmission and once jobsDB Hong Kong receives it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while jobsDB Hong Kong strives to protect Users' personal information and data against unauthorized access, jobsDB Hong Kong cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Retention of Personal Data

Once jobsDB Hong Kong has obtained a User's personal information and/or data, it will be maintained securely in jobsDB Hong Kong's system. Subject to legal requirements, the personal information and/or data of Users will be retained by jobsDB Hong Kong after deactivation of the relevant service until Users request jobsDB Hong Kong to erase his/her own personal information and/or data from jobsDB Hong Kong's database or to terminate his/her membership of the Site.

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

jobsDB Hong Kong reserves the right to update, revise, modify or amend this Privacy Statement in the following manner at any time as jobsDB Hong Kong deems necessary, so Users are strongly recommended to review this Privacy Statement frequently. If jobsDB Hong Kong decides to update, revise, modify or amend this Privacy Statement, jobsDB Hong Kong will post those changes to this webpage and/or other places jobsDB Hong Kong deems appropriate so that Users would be aware of what information jobsDB Hong Kong collects, how jobsDB Hong Kong uses it, and under what circumstances, if any, jobsDB Hong Kong discloses it.

If jobsDB Hong Kong makes material changes to this Privacy Statement, jobsDB Hong Kong will notify Users on this webpage, by email, or by means of a notice on the home page of jobsDB Hong Kong.

## Enquiries

Should you have any enquiries, please email at [cs@jobsdb.com](mailto:cs@jobsdb.com), telephone at +852 2332-8832 or write to us at the following address:

jobsDB Hong Kong  
11/F, guardian house  
32 oi kwan road, wan chai, hong kong
